[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[The Spring of the Sword]
[Episode 8]
A miserable actress like you
He doesn't deserve to live in the Danyue Pavilion!
Concubine Xia died that night.
But was it a coincidence?
Or is there something more behind it?
It's very difficult to say.
Maybe...
Maybe
My mother knows more.
[Tingyun Pavilion]
Qingyuan.
Qinghe.
I have suffered since I was little,
I beg you to have compassion on me.
What are you doing?
Please ask Mrs. Lian
Tell me what happened that year.
Qingyuan.
[Tingyun Pavilion]
Mother.
This is tea made from buds freshly harvested this year,
It's very fresh.
If you like it,
I will send for more at the Danyue Pavilion.
Thank you very much, Mrs. Lian.
Your visit is what I value most.
since I arrived at this mansion.
You helped Qinghe the other day,
I owe you a big favor,
So I came to see you right away.
Qinghe is my good sister.
As well as
you and my mother,
I suppose you two
They also had a strong sisterly bond, right?
My mother always said
that you were in this residence
her closest sister.
The mirror polisher works really well.
look,
Even the eyebrows are reflected in every defined hair.
Since the master returned from visiting,
He only lived in the Luoying Pavilion
or at the Liuhua Residence,
We couldn't even see it.
Who cares if you have mountain eyebrows?
or willow eyebrows?
What happened?
The boss
Did he stay in your room?
Only the first few days when he returned last month.
By the way,
stop taking
that recipe I gave you.
Contains Xiamaxian,
an herb that draws water from the body through urine and feces,
And that's precisely why it can also cause an abortion.
If you get pregnant this time,
Continuing to take it would be bad for your body.
I know,
I've already stopped taking that medicine.
I hope you can this time
to have a son.
I like daughters better.
Your Qinghe is so good,
So pretty.
Without a son,
the mother and sisters
They will suffer together.
Mrs. Jin!
Ms. Xia has come furiously to the Danyue Pavilion looking for her,
I don't know what he wants.
I'm going to see what happened.
Chunqing!
Mother.
Why are you so distracted today?
Is it because of Qingyuan?
Chunqing always
He has been kind.
However, in this mansion,
The most useless thing is kindness.
What does he mean by that?
Qingyuan.
Excuse me.
But back then,
I was there too
in a difficult situation.
Do you mean
Does the death of the concubine Xia have anything to do with you?
How could that be?
Except that...
When I gave the Xiamaxian to Cui'er,
I didn't know they were going to use it to hurt someone.
I didn't imagine
that Mrs. Xia...
Mrs. Xia,
Mrs. Jin asked me to bring her this pregnancy medicine,
and said that soon
I would vacate the Danyue Pavilion so that you could live there.
Leave it there.
Come! Mrs. Xia is dead!
I never imagined that Mrs. Xia
I would die for this.
And I least expected it
that Chunqing would leave
the mansion for this.
Cui'er.
Tell me,
How did the concubine Xia die?
Speaks!
Was...
Mrs. Jin gave me some pregnancy medicine.
and she asked me to take it to Mrs. Xia.
Cui'er.
You...
I didn't do anything!
Do you still dare to deny it?
[Qinyue Gallery]
With Mei Yinghua and Nana Rong pressing on,
and Qinghe so small,
I didn't dare challenge them
and to tell the truth.
I was forced
to be his accomplice.
I thought
since Chunqing was innocent,
The truth would be revealed someday.
Besides,
The boss probably wouldn't want to punish her.
- I wasn't expecting that. - So what?
You're covering up for the real guilt.
How will the truth be revealed?
Qingyuan!
I should apologize to you
and with your mother.
I owe my life to your mother.
You can take it now!
I saved
These words in my heart
for more than six thousand days and nights.
Now that I'm saying them in front of you,
I feel liberated.
Mrs. Lian.
Believe
that your repentance is sincere.
My mother's spirit in heaven
I certainly wouldn't want to make you suffer.
But now those things have come to this,
What's the point?
Blame?
Qingyuan.
Things in the Xie family
They are deeper than you imagine,
And it's not something a girl like you can understand.
Besides,
You still depend on the Xie family
to find a good marriage.
If your mother were still alive,
I wouldn't want you to ruin your future either.
Finding a good marriage?
And then what?
To be like you,
trembling with fear,
terrified all day?
Or like my mother,
being incriminated,
suffering all kinds of humiliations?
Mrs. Lian.
Now Qinghe is at its peak.
You should think it through carefully.
If you continue to be so naive,
who used the Xiamaxian
to kill the concubine Xia
He could now kill inside the residence
19 years ago.
Do you really think it will let you prosper?
My life doesn't matter.
I just hope
that Qinghe can get married soon
and that you too can get married soon.
You two
They must get away from this cursed place
as far away as possible.
[Danyue Pavilion]
Have some tea, ma'am.
Thanks for your help,
We were able to finalize the link between Qinghe
and the Pei family.
You are a great benefactor of the Xie mansion!
It's not that big of a deal.
It's Mrs. Xie's good fortune.
Actually,
I have come today
to tell him
Good news.
What news?
That's good news,
The best of all!
What is it about?
Since
This lucky star came to the Xie family,
the good news
They haven't stopped.
It's true.
I'm going to play matchmaker!
For the Xie family!
Tell us.
Lady,
Don't leave us in suspense.
The heir of the Marquis of Danyang
He has set his sights on one of his young ladies.
Are you referring to Chunzhi?
Yeah.
Exact.
I know that the Marquis's wife and Wenzhuo have a good relationship,
I'm just acting as an intermediary.
Which of our
Ladies, do you like it?
Who else could it be but Qingru?
I can't wait to attend the wedding banquet!
from Chunzhi and Qingru!
To Qingru and Chunzhi
I watched them grow up since they were children.
Excellent
that these two have characters
so compatible.
Do you know?
Chunzhi will eventually be mine.
I am glad that Mrs. Xie also agrees to this marriage.
The wife of the Marquis of Danyang
He also greatly appreciates Miss Qingru.
Mr. Chunzhi and Miss Qingru
They are undoubtedly a perfect couple,
well matched in position and appearance.
However,
Mr. Chunzhi
He has his own ideas.
That's why he asked me to eat.
to gauge the opinion of the Xie family.
Lady,
What does he mean by that?
Just say so, don't worry.
Yesterday
The marquis's wife came to find me
saying that his son since the Shangsi Festival
has lost his appetite.
He asked her what was wrong.
But he said nothing.
She worried a lot,
He questioned the servant.
It turns out that
Mr. Chunzhi
He has fallen in love with Miss Qingyuan,
But he doesn't know if she feels the same way.
And that's why he's so restless.
How can she be?
But
The marquis's wife has heard some rumors
and has been somewhat influenced,
especially regarding Miss Qingyuan and Mr. Yan.
Mrs. Xie,
Don't be offended.
Qingyuan has bad luck,
He has barely returned to my side,
with that origin
And so much gossip on top of that,
It seems she is not destined
to become linked to a family
so distinguished.
Did you hear that?
Grandma already said it,
Chunzhi is unattainable for you.
Forget that idea!
Yeah.
Then I congratulate you
for your happy union with Mr. Chunzhi.
Stop pretending.
I know you don't have good intentions!
Qingrong.
And what's it to you?
It just is!
There is still a distinguished guest here.
What are they doing?
They have no manners whatsoever.
Report!
Mrs. Xie,
Mr. Chunzhi has arrived.
He brought gifts for Miss Qingru,
Miss Qingrong and Miss Qingyuan.
Do you like them?
Miss Qingrong,
This mother-of-pearl mirror
It's been hard to get lately.
Mr. Li,
Where did you get it?
Qingru's jade pendant is more beautiful,
elegant and refined,
It fits you perfectly.
How gorgeous.
Chunzhi,
Does it fit well?
Qingyuan.
Mr. Chunzhi.
Qingyuan,
We haven't seen each other since the Shangsi Festival.
I've been thinking about you a lot,
That's why I came to visit you.
I brought a humble gift.
It is agarwood.
I thought it would be something special,
It turns out it's agarwood.
Agarwood calms the mind and helps with sleep.
It's good medicine.
Thank you, Mr. Chunzhi.
Then I won't bother you anymore.
I'm leaving.
Qingyuan.
Do you think the gift is too common?
It is not common agarwood.
He is from Yazhou.
Yazhou?
Yazhou agarwood?
This...
That's worth more than gold!
Miss Qingyuan,
Mrs. Hu requests your presence in the reception hall.
Mr. Yan.
I've heard about the insolent servant incident at the Xie mansion,
So I prepared some treasures especially
to calm Miss Qingyuan.
Treasures are good,
But when is he going to stop?
of imitating others, Mr. Yan?
And that lipstick from the Liuxiang store…
Did he learn it from the girls at the brothel?
to please people?
This lipstick color
I chose it especially for you,
It looks better in the light
of the candles.
Hope!
Mr. Yan.
Mr. Yan, how generous you are.
To make a beautiful lady smile,
Everything must be top-notch.
Mr. Zhengjun, I've heard you're an expert in antiques.
What if
Are you checking out these gifts for your sister?
Okay, okay, okay.
The patina on this jade vase
It's beautiful!
Mr. Yan.
Excellent,
This is truly excellent.
Oh, really?
This antiquity was recommended by Magistrate Guo,
I'm sure it's authentic.
Ah, Guo Baofeng?
Then you found the right person.
He has many good qualities.
Qingyuan.
Gifts are valued for their quality.
not because of their quantity.
If you like vulgar things,
Next time I can give them to you too.
Mr. Chunzhi,
I have to go find Qinghe,
Goodbye.
Wait.
I prepared these gifts with such care,
Miss Qingyuan, but you don't even look at them,
I am very hurt.
I see very clearly
your effort.
But here there are those who know how to appreciate treasures.
Not even with eight gift boxes
They manage to get her to stay, right?
It's true.
What a pity.
How wonderful!
This is really good.
[Danyue Pavilion]
Miss,
Those two came back to cause trouble again.
Qingru, Qingrong.
[Qinyue Gallery]
Baoxian, prepare tea.
Yeah.
It's rare for them to come to the Danyue Pavilion.
[Qinyue Gallery]
Do you need anything?
What are you pretending?
You congratulated me insincerely before,
but who knows what spell
You did it to Chunzhi
to steal her soul completely.
Exact!
This bitch
He doesn't say a single word of truth.
I didn't do anything.
Chunzhi and I alone...
Only what?
He gave you
Agarwood is quite expensive, isn't it?
Agarwood...
I already gave it to Qinghe.
Did you give it to Qinghe?
By what right?
You...
What are you hiding?
"Chunzhi didn't give it to me!" "How dare you hide it?"
Qingru, quickly!
Give it back to me!
Liar!
Such precious jade...
If Chunzhi didn't give it to you,
Did you steal it?
Since you like it, Qingru,
I'll give it to you.
It's yours now.
You're almost engaged
with Mr. Chunzhi,
I
I would never dare to have those illusions.
It's good that you know.
Wait for me.
Let me see it.
I won't show you.
Stingy.
Guo,
Are you still in the mood to get drunk?
You recommended an antique to Mr. Yan
without consulting me.
Get up, get up. Wake up.
Wake up!
Why are you looking for me?
Mother.
Good.
Mr. Zhengjun, what's wrong?
So restless from an early age.
Did something happen to you last night when you went out?
My son is very lucky, what could possibly happen to him?
TRUE?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's just that I didn't sleep well last night.
And I'm a little sleepy.
Mrs. hum,
don't worry.
If nothing happens, all the better.
Zhengjun,
as a descendant of the Xie family,
You need to know how important your responsibility is.
Don't let your guard down
Whatever happens,
And don't give cause for criticism
against the family due to negligence.
Yeah,
I will follow your teachings, Grandma.
Eat.
Your favorite,
eat more.
Excuse me, Mr. Yan.
This case was investigated by the government.
We shouldn't bother him,
But the identity of the deceased is special.
By the way, Mr. Yan, look,
This was found in him.
"I did all this by myself, Guo Baofeng."
My gambling addiction ruined my family.
I regret it and I am ashamed.
But Xie Zhengjun also participated in the division of the loot."
[The guilty servant, Guo Baofeng]
Mr. Yan.
Suicide,
letter of confession.
Everything so well arranged,
as if he was afraid we would discover something.
Do you mean
that Guo Baofeng gave his life to cover for someone
And did he deliberately lead us to investigate Xie Zhengjun?
So, that person...
Who else could it be?
Baofeng!
I arrived late!
Baofeng, why did you do it!
Baofeng!
What pain you have caused me!
Mr. Wei.
My condolences.
But take care, don't let the pain consume you.
Magistrate Guo
He left something behind before he died.
Take a look.
Miss,
He was right!
It seems Mr. Zhengjun really got himself into big trouble.
It was just a hunch.
His behavior today was very strange.
Although I don't know where he was yesterday,
Something must have happened.
That's easy.
If something important happened in Hengtang,
Just ask Mr. Yan.
Do I have to ask him?
Baofeng and Mr. Zhengjun
They were very good friends.
But why
Was he involved in this corruption case?
Mr. Wei,
Mr. Yan recently investigated
the murder of the foreman
And the clues led right to Magistrate Guo.
And now, what a coincidence, it turns out he died.
Who do you think
What should they answer?
Do you mean that
Did Baofeng order the foreman to be killed?
No, no, no.
That's absolutely impossible, Mr. Yan!
There must be something hidden.
Baofeng was always a fearful man.
If he wasn't manipulated by someone bad,
He would never have dared to do such a crazy thing.
But we just examined the body
And it is clearly suicide.
However, whether he was threatened or not,
We don't know that.
Mr. Yan,
Do you have any suspects?
I still don't have any leads.
Mr. Wei,
Could you give me some guidance?
Mr. Yan,
There are things I shouldn't say,
But given the circumstances,
with such clear evidence,
I have no choice but to speak.
The death of Guo Baofeng
and food for the victims
They are definitely related to Mr. Zhengjun.
Do you wish
investigate the Xie family thoroughly?
So, Mr. Wei, you want me to investigate
What?
No kidding, Sir Ysn.
This matter is not trivial.
Only you can decide personally.
I only give
my humble opinion
considering the stability of the court.
SW
I must be even more cautious.
If I judge incorrectly,
I could end up being accused myself.
After all, in this court
There is no shortage of those who
They want me dead.
Qingyuan, are you really not worried at all?
If it's as you say,
[Fuyu Pavilion]
the death of Guo Baofeng
It wasn't suicide,
but a premeditated murder.
And Zhengjun happens to be involved in all of this.
Yan Rui is cunning, he won't let
That's just how things are.
Xie Zhengjun has always been a loudmouth.
Wei Changyan doesn't dare bet
that he hasn't told the secret,
That's why he acted first.
He's not stupid.
If I don't take action against the Xie family,
He and Xie Shu are going to be together,
and without anything happening to him.
On the contrary,
If I send Xie Zhengjun to the gallows...
The two times Yan Rui caused trouble,
He only asked for money and food.
If he really comes this time,
I suppose their goal will be the same.
Calm,
Grandma won't let him do whatever he wants.
But we go up
who interfered with the food of the victims,
That's a serious crime.
If the emperor finds out about this,
The least that can happen is that dad and older brother
lose their positions,
And worst of all, the entire Xie family will be banished.
Councilor Xie is a third-ranking official,
with disciples and allies in all ministries.
If we truly confront each other,
We will be seriously injured.
What if the emperor finds out about this?
Qinghe,
You greatly underestimate the prestige of a father in court.
Si Yan Rui
dares to touch a single tile belonging to the Xie family,
tomorrow
The Imperial Court of Censorship will accuse him of everything.
Even if he is the emperor's favorite,
I'm sure he'll think twice before getting involved in something like that.
He wants Xie Shu and me
Let's fight until we destroy each other
so that he can take advantage of the opportunity.
Then we can only pretend we don't know anything.
The death of Guo Baofeng is clearly suspicious.
And furthermore,
although everyone goes their own way,
I don't think it's that cruel
how to
leave no way out.
Since Wei Changyan wants to be the fisherman,
I will send a giant wave after him.
[Xie Family of Hengtang]
The Xie family is a powerful family from Hengtang,
How did she suddenly find herself surrounded by soldiers?
I heard that
The second son in his family committed a great crime.
Oh really?
It enraged the emperor.
It will surely involve the entire Xie mansion.
What are they doing?
They entered the Xie mansion without permission,
Don't they understand the law?
We have orders to arrest the criminal Xie Zhengjun.
I hope you don't obstruct.
What happened to Zhengjun?
Who dares to be so insolent in the Xie mansion?
Mrs. Xie,
The Office of Criminal Justice is investigating.
[Edict]
I hope you will forgive me.
They are looking!
Wait!
This is the private area where the women of the family reside!
This is outrageous!
Stop!
Stop now!
[Jingmu Hall]
Yes,
You hadn't been here for a long time.
I've been busy lately, Grandma.
It's been a long time since I've had pear blossom milk.
Come on.
Take.
Granny,
I never sugarcoat this.
I'm old now, I forgot.
Yunya is the one who likes honey.
I'll trade you.
It doesn't matter,
That's how I see it.
Then I'll give you a box
loquat sweets,
They are good for the lungs.
Business hasn't been going well lately.
I've prepared many.
They're not leftovers,
They are fresh.
Since Yunya went to the Xie mansion,
He almost didn't come back.
He always sent a message
if I couldn't return.
But lately the Xie mansion has been in trouble
and I haven't heard anything from her.
I'm very worried.
that is affected.
Let me go!
What's with all the noise?
at this hour of the night?
Grandmother!
Zhengjun!
Mrs. Hu!
Save me!
- Son! - Save me!
Mother!
Help me!
Are!
- Save me! - Let him go!
Let me through!
Mother!
Mr. Yan has arrived!
Mr. Yan,
The criminal has been captured.
This individual attempted to resist arrest.
Is this how the Xie family treats visitors?
They really surprised me.
I didn't kill anyone!
Mom, please help me!
Mr. Yan,
If I followed the rules of courtesy towards a visitor,
The Xie mansion would treat him with respect.
But now he's coming with soldiers,
blocking and arresting people,
causing a huge scandal.
Have you thought about how this will end?
My eldest son and my eldest grandson
They have protected the northern border for the emperor for years!
- You... - That's why
I came to guard the granary in the name of the emperor.
You should thank me,
because I'm doing him a favor
Councilor Xie cleaning his own house.
Let me go!
Fan Zhong.
Xie Zhengjun,
second son of the Xie family of Hengtang,
in collusion with Magistrate Guo Baofeng,
exchanged 162,000 kilos of official rice destined for emergency aid,
replacing it with old bran instead of quality grain,
harming the victims.
When he was discovered,
Xie Zhengjun murdered magistrate Guo Baofeng.
He faked suicide
trying to hide his crime.
Now, according to the Penal Code, Volume Two,
Immediate capture is authorized
of the main suspect, Xie Zhengjun
remaining in the custody of the Court for trial.
Once the facts were clarified,
The culprit will be beheaded.
The Xie mansion will be confiscated and sealed.
their assets will be transferred to the country,
and all relatives within the third degree of kinship
They will be exiled.
Mother! Zhengjun!
Zhengjun, Zhengjun...
Your sins are so grave
that I shouldn't have saved you.
Lie!
Don't blame me!
Take it away!
- Mr. Yan! - Yes!
Wait!
The Penal Code, Volume Seven, clearly states
that the residences of third-rank or higher officials
they cannot be raided
unless it is a case of treason.
Volume 12 also establishes
that when relatives of third-rank or higher officials
are involved in litigation,
The Imperial Clan Affairs Court must intervene.
Mr. Yan,
Since he's going to investigate,
Why doesn't he stay temporarily according to Article 36?
And wait for the Imperial Clan Affairs Court to send someone to coordinate?
The east wing has very good light,
everyone at the Xie mansion
They will be able to hear
his daily teachings.
Miss Qingyuan,
You know the laws very well.
What if
From now on you will accompany me
And you spend your time copying files for me?
Yan Rui!
What's wrong, Mrs. Xie?
Could it be the red paper you sent me
Wasn't it so that I could be closer to Miss Qingyuan?
Everyone, listen to the order!
Wait for instructions.
Yeah!
They're out!
It's out! It's out!
Mr. Yan's order!
Guard the Xie mansion,
Keep a close eye on things!
Nobody can leave even one step!
Yeah!
Get out of the way!
It is...
Isn't that it?
[Xie Family of Hengtang]
Mr. Zhengjun from your family?
I've heard that after spring, begins
You suffer from a nighttime cough.
I prepared this especially for you
kumquats and fritillaria bulb.
It took me quite a bit of effort.
Well.
They don't need to pick it up anymore.
They may leave.
Miss Qingyuan, please
to make my bed.
Since he has surrounded the Xie mansion,
Killing or torturing us is just a matter of one word.
Why bother my grandmother?
She is elderly
and cannot bear such a fright.
Stop.
SW,
Why did you hide for so long?
Are you forcing me to act this way?
Is there really nothing in this world?
Why do you care?
That's interesting what you say, Mr. Yan.
After all,
This is all theater.
Who is more noble than the other?
So, you blame me?
For dismantling your stage?
It doesn't matter.
Anyway, this work
I don't want to act it out with you.
♪ Wild geese climb into dense clouds, waiting for the moon to rest ♪
What if I insist on changing your mind?
Aren't you afraid?
that one wrong step will make
the one who wields the knife
♪ Old memories weigh heavily, haunting every dream ♪
Will I get hurt?
♪ Ascent and fall alternate ♪
You don't dare.
♪ Phases of the moon, waxing and waning without planning ♪
♪ Count the fallen flowers, never count all the sorrows of parting ♪
♪ You, tender yet sharp, with thorns by your side ♪
That?
Do you think I dare now?
Qingyuan.
♪ Like a dim but burning candle ♪
I remember telling you
That's what I like most in life.
It's about softening hard bones.
♪ The sign of wind and rain, the path stretches far away ♪
♪ Flowers float on the current, affections gently awaken ♪
The harder the bone
♪ Half reality, half illusion, a cup of spring awakens me ♪
I like it more.
♪ Consumed and freed, held by the hand of destiny ♪
♪ To the soft, warm breeze of the sunset, the candles return home ♪
♪ Fine moonbeams weave dreams all night long ♪